<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pokhari.com</title>
    <link>https://pokhari.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pokhari.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pokhari.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Study Ecology in Norway</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/study-ecology-in-norway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/study-ecology-in-norway/</guid>
      <description> University of Oslo Programs:  Biodiversity and Systematics (master&amp;rsquo;s two years):  Norwegian University of Life Sciences Programs:  Master of Science in Ecology Master of Science in Agroecology  Important Information:  How to apply Documentation of Financing Application Portal  Norwegian University of Science and Technology Programs:  Industrial Ecology  Inland Norway University of Applied Sciences Programs:  Master in Applied Ecology  University of Bergen Programs:  Biodiversity, Evolution and Ecology  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combine separate odd and even PDF files in Mac</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/combine-separate-odd-even-pdf-files-in-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 04:05:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/combine-separate-odd-even-pdf-files-in-mac/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it is necessary to combine two PDF files one with only even pages and one with only odd pages. Mac Automator can do this task very easily. Just make your PDF files ready and follow the following steps:
Open Automator Automator is shipped with any Mac. It has many awesome feature that can save your precious time at many occasions. For this task, first open Automator either from application launchpad or from spotlight light search or from application folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 06:42:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Along with Ford Prefect, Dent barely escapes the Earth&amp;rsquo;s destruction as it is demolished to make way for a hyperspace bypass. Arthur spends the next several years, still wearing his dressing gown, helplessly launched from crisis to crisis while trying to straighten out his lifestyle.
 He rather enjoys tea, but seems to have trouble obtaining it in the far reaches of the galaxy.
 In time, he learns how to fly and carves a niche for himself as a sandwich-maker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>colophon</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/colophon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 06:28:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/colophon/</guid>
      <description>This website is a personal homepage.
The site is built with Hugo—a static site generator made with Go. The website source code is available on GitHub. It uses the cocoa theme. The posts are written in Markdown.
The primary font face is Open Sans and the monospace font face is Ubuntu Mono. The social icons are from the Ionicons font set. CSS classes for code syntax highlighting are inserted during compile-time by Hugo using Pygments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 20:29:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/code/</guid>
      <description>The Hitchhiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy is a comedy science fiction series created by Douglas Adams. Originally a radio comedy broadcast on BBC Radio 4 in 1978, it was later adapted to other formats, and over several years it gradually became an international multi-media phenomenon. Adaptations have included stage shows, a &amp;ldquo;trilogy&amp;rdquo; of five books published between 1979 and 1992, a sixth novel penned by Eoin Colfer in 2009, a 1981 TV series, a 1984 computer game, and three series of three-part comic book adaptations of the first three novels published by DC Comics between 1993 and 1996.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have a sushi with Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/have-a-sushi-with-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/have-a-sushi-with-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>If you love quick preview feature in MacOS and you are missing that in your ubuntu, have a sushi and you will be satisfied. Even if you are not a MacOS user, you will get so used to with sushi that you will never get satisfied. You might be thinking what I am babbling about. I am talking about a quick preview of most of the popular file in ubuntu that is provided by gnome-sushi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>