<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Pokhari.com</title>
    <link>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Pokhari.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pokhari.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Study Ecology in Norway</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/study-ecology-in-norway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/study-ecology-in-norway/</guid>
      <description> University of Oslo Programs:  Biodiversity and Systematics (master&amp;rsquo;s two years):  Norwegian University of Life Sciences Programs:  Master of Science in Ecology Master of Science in Agroecology  Important Information:  How to apply Documentation of Financing Application Portal  Norwegian University of Science and Technology Programs:  Industrial Ecology  Inland Norway University of Applied Sciences Programs:  Master in Applied Ecology  University of Bergen Programs:  Biodiversity, Evolution and Ecology  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combine separate odd and even PDF files in Mac</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/combine-separate-odd-even-pdf-files-in-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 04:05:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/combine-separate-odd-even-pdf-files-in-mac/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it is necessary to combine two PDF files one with only even pages and one with only odd pages. Mac Automator can do this task very easily. Just make your PDF files ready and follow the following steps:
Open Automator Automator is shipped with any Mac. It has many awesome feature that can save your precious time at many occasions. For this task, first open Automator either from application launchpad or from spotlight light search or from application folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have a sushi with Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/have-a-sushi-with-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pokhari.github.io/blog/have-a-sushi-with-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>If you love quick preview feature in MacOS and you are missing that in your ubuntu, have a sushi and you will be satisfied. Even if you are not a MacOS user, you will get so used to with sushi that you will never get satisfied. You might be thinking what I am babbling about. I am talking about a quick preview of most of the popular file in ubuntu that is provided by gnome-sushi.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>